<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi there! on Jelle Langedijk</title>
    <link>https://jellela.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hi there! on Jelle Langedijk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 21:05:58 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jellela.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>https://jellela.github.io/profile/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 21:50:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jellela.github.io/profile/profile/</guid>
      <description>This page contains my professional profile. This is merely intended to give a &amp;ldquo;quick&amp;rdquo; overview, my curriculum vitae is available here as .pdf. Home address and phone number are excluded for privacy reasons. Information seen below might be more up to date than the .pdf.
Education Huygens Lyceum Eindhoven | Natuur en Techniek 2012-2018
Completed the final exam Atheneum in the program Nature &amp;amp; Technology with favorable consequence. Graduated in the Dutch, English and French Language and Literature, Mathematics (B &amp;amp; D), Physics, Chemistry and Management and Organization (MO).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jellela.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 16:52:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jellela.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>This is the first ever website that I&amp;rsquo;ve written using Markdown, html and css. All these components are &amp;ldquo;combined&amp;rdquo; using the HUGO framework and hosted via Github Pages. Feel free to contact me via Email </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The website is up!</title>
      <link>https://jellela.github.io/blog/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jellela.github.io/blog/blog1/</guid>
      <description>This is the first blog post on the website, made just before the website was deployed for the first time via GitHub pages! The website is still a &amp;ldquo;work in progress&amp;rdquo;, but came at a point where it is ready enough to share with the world.
The LinkedIn post related to the launch of the website can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
